(Sheldon:)Wrong. And let's keep it clean, shall we?
Kangaroo. Uh, l'd be a kangajew...
(Howard:)...the first of my people
to dunk a basketball.
Also, instead ofjust living in your mother's
house, you could live inside her body.
(Sheldon:)Clever, but also wrong.
(Sheldon:)No. The best organism for human beings
to merge with is the lichen itseIf.
(Sheldon:)That way you'd be
human, fungus and algae.
(Sheldon:)Triple threat.
(Sheldon:)Like three-bean salad.
(Leonard:)Give me one circumstance
that would be useful.
(Sheldon:)All right, picture this.
A beautiful outdoor concert.
(Sheldon:)Now, as a human,
l appreciate Beethoven.
(Sheldon:)As a fungus, I have a terrific view
growing out of a towering maple tree.
(Sheldon:)And no thank you expensive concessions
because as an algae...
(Sheldon:)...I'll just snack on this sunlight.
- He got us again.
- No, he didn't.
(Raj:)Anyway, if it's okay with you,
we should talk about Howard's bachelor party.